Hello friends, welcome to
our channel Smart Solution. Today we have brought you the
Family Sealed Policy of ICICI Bank General Insurance. We will discuss the
entire policy, what is included in the insurance
policy, how does it work and who
can take it.  In how much rupees you will
get the policy, how much rupees will be insured,
to get complete information about this video,
watch the video till the end. If you are
new to our channel, then subscribe to the channel
because we provide a
lot of information and facts on banking insurance and cryptocurrency.
Friends, let's start today's video with
ICICI Bank
General Insurance's Family Shield, in which
you can take a term plan ranging from 10 lakhs to crores of rupees,
i.e. an accident
insurance policy.
You get this policy at a very cheap and reasonable rate.
I am with you today,
Insurance and Banking,
Jyoti Madam. If someone buys this policy, a
salaried person can take 10 times his income at that time, if he
is self-employed, he can take 20 times
his income. And if someone has
no income, no proof
of income, he can buy this insurance up to 10 lakhs, that is,
anyone from the poorest of the poor to the richest of the rich, can
buy this policy.  Next, we will
talk about all the benefits of this. The calculations
we will make today will all be done
under the insurance of one crore, that is, any
person who takes out an insurance of one crore will get this insurance.
How much
premium will he have to pay? Approximately, he will have to pay a premium of Rs. 12,940.
Along with this, friends, the special
feature of this is that anyone between the ages of 18 and 65 can
take this insurance.
And he can renew it up
to the age of 116 years, that is,
even after 65 years, he can renew this insurance.
You can renew this insurance up to the age of 80 years, 90 years, 100 years, 116 years
and take the benefit till its last.
What are the benefits?
Madam, first of all, what are the benefits? I will tell you
all the benefits. I just wanted to
tell you that by paying Rs. 940, you
can get an insurance of one crore, but it depends on
your income. If someone does
not have any income proof, someone is poor, then he
can get his insurance up to one lakh rupees. The
annual premium for him will be around Rs. 90.  Let's
talk about it.
If someone takes an insurance policy worth a crore rupees,
what benefits will they get? We are talking about
Jyoti ma'am's benefits.
Everything else, as I have explained to you,
can be extended by paying for it for so many years. Okay,
let's discuss the
benefits and benefits. There are many.
Some of the main benefits of taking any plan are that
first of all,
what will the children do after you leave? The second plan is
how will the children be educated? If
someone in your family falls ill, what facilities will you provide for them? The
person who is leaving and has left?
Okay, what did you leave behind? What did you
give to your family? The most important thing is
what will be the condition of your family
after you leave? First of all, the education of your children. Let's
assume that you are taking an insurance policy for one person.
Okay, you are taking an insurance policy worth a crore.
And your children  Now your
child has taken NEET, someone has
become a professor, and what is important for them to study?
You would like your children to
study like my descendants, someone has become a professor, someone has
become an engineer, and first of all, what is
your education benefit, which is the most
important education benefit, you will
get an education benefit of one lakh rupees with an insurance of one crore.
Your
children who have studied up to 10 lakhs
can do
whatever they want
in the university without any worries because up to 10 lakhs they have very
good education plans,
because I am a student, I know this place has a
very good education system,
study abroad, even if you study in your own country, it
comes second, please take some respect for yourself. Now you get into an
accident or any part of your body
becomes disabled, do not let any
part of it become disabled,
accept that it is not now, he is in work.
And at that time, even if you have a
burnt limb,
what will you get if it is burnt? The company will give you a benefit of up to two lakh rupees. I am
counting the riders. Basically, keep in mind that I am
on benefit. Up to one crore is a benefit.
What benefits do you get along with it? The
most important thing comes after that.
Suppose now you have gone somewhere.
After going, you have
some problem due to an accident etc.
You have a condition of permanent disability etc.
And at that time, your
family will also be given an insurance of up to one crore.
Okay, next
comes. Believe me, now you are
not on permanent disability. Suppose
you had to be hospitalized for some time. You had to
stay in the hospital due to an
accident. Okay, and at that time, what will happen to
you, sir? The company that
supports your lifestyle and family.  Total
Hajj will keep giving you weekly benefits,
next time it comes, like a bone
breaking, a soft bone, a case of a bone, and it happens to
everyone. Take care of yourself. If an
accident happens and a bone breaks, if a
person's bone breaks, the
company will
give you benefits of up to 10 lakhs, up to 10 lakhs. That's why it is important that you
take some other benefits with you in your life. It is
important that you take a little, not just this time, you get the medicine and you do
n't wake up with it.
You take a lot with it. Just like the education of children is the
most important. Right, in the second,
in the time of your medicine, which you have sat on the bed at that time, you will also face
someone and that time,
Things keep coming to us
and that is why it
is necessary and necessary to do it, so
take it today, not just today, take it now, it is necessary.
In this, I would like to discuss very
well. If you have rabies and tetanus related
hospitalization,
you will have to pay up to Rs. 1 lakh. In
this, your doctor should prescribe it first. Do not
prescribe it. If someone
bites a dog, then get the
tetanus vaccine. The most
important thing is to get it within a week. If you
forget to take it,
you have work. You had to go to a meeting.
You forgot. God
forbid, something happened. A dog died of acid poisoning.
You will get a million rupees. So, if the dog
dies, you will not get such a job.
No one knows about it. No one knows about
any policy, policy at all.  Family Insurance is
basically an accidental plan that will work only in case of an accident. As
Astra told you, if a person becomes
partially disabled, he will be disabled as much as he can due to an accident. If
you are 4,
you will get this insurance. Yes, we
all mean that accident cases are very rare. If a
person has an accident, but he does not
know who it is, it can be
anyone. That is why
we insure our lives to protect ourselves,
not to die.
Friends, it is important to tell you that this accident is
basically an accident base plan. Accident does
not mean that it is a road
accident, an accident of any kind, an
accident, you fell from the house, you fell from the car, you
worked in the field, you were working there, you were injured.  There are
many reasons for an accident, an
accident means any sudden
death, which should not have happened,
that accident is covered in it. In
this, I will
tell you that total disability means that you become
disabled and are not fit to earn money,
but you will get Rs. 10 crore.
Partial disability means that you become disabled, as many as you can,
you have a pen, a
10-year-old, and today you will know that we are
behind you. We have lost the corona virus
and the one that is still a virus and many
viruses that are still used by the people of the country. According to the
benefits of the beneficiaries, the
benefit is different. The infection gets into the body along with the nervous system. You
can also take a lakh plan for that. Friends, with this, we are
taking today's video towards the end
and we request you
that if you have listened to the video completely and did
not understand anything, then
we are here for you. Yes, and we are here for you.  We
will tell you in detail and if
you want to get this or any other policy or
insurance, then you
can come and meet us at our office.
We have put our contact number
in the description, you
can also call us.
Thank you all very much for watching the video in full.